http://www.lafgroup.com/index.php/privacy-statement

ARCHITECTS
LAF SolutionsSub MenuFireBuilding Code RegulationsFire Protection DesignFire UpgradeFire TestingFire Proofing Materials And SystemsFire Resisting ConstructionDamper Inspection / MaintenanceFire Proof InstallationAcousticSound Insertion LossNoise Reduction SystemsVermiculite CeilingThermalProblem SolvingSectorsBuildingStructural Fire ProtectionSeparating Fire ProtectionMEP Services Fire ProtectionOil & GasInfrastructureMiningAgricultureProductsOur ProductsOur SystemsPassive SystemAcoustic SystemDivisionsManufacturingConsultancyContractingClick here for site map
ENGINEERS
LAF SolutionsSub MenuFireFire Protection DesignFire TestingFire Proofing Materials And SystemsFire Resisting ConstructionBuilding Code RegulationsDamper Inspection / MaintenanceFire Proof InstallationAcousticThermalProblem SolvingSectorsBuildingStructural Fire ProtectionSeparating Fire ProtectionMEP Services Fire ProtectionInfrastructureMiningOil & GasAgricultureProductsOur ProductsVermitex® AFVermitex® THVermiduct®Vermitex Acustico®Vermitex® 7FSClick here for other productsOur SystemsPassive SystemsAcoustic SystemsDivisionsManufacturingConsultancyContractingClick here for site map
BUILDERS
LAF SolutionsSub MenuFireBuilding Code RegulationsDamper Inspection / MaintenanceFire Protection DesignFire Proofing Materials And SystemsFire Resisting ConstructionFire UpgradeFire TestingFire Proof InstallationAcousticVermiculite CeilingSound Insertion LossNoise Reduction SystemsThermalProblem SolvingSectorsBuildingStructural Fire ProtectionSeparating Fire ProtectionMEP Services Fire ProtectionPenetrations & Fire StopsElastomeric PadsInfrastructureTunnelsBridges MiningSeparating VentilationOil & Gas AgricultureProductsOur ProductsVermitex® AFVermitex® THVermiduct®Vermitex Acustico®Foamed Vermitex® Click here for other productsOur SystemsPassive SystemsAcoustic SystemsDivisionsManufacturingConsultancyContractingClick here for site map
APPLICATORS
LAF SolutionsProductsOur ProductsVermitex® AFVermitex® THVermiduct®Vermitex Acustico®Foamed Vermitex®Vermitex® 7FSClick here for other productsOur SystemsPassive SystemStructural SteelStructural DeckingConcrete Upgrade (Cellulosic Fire)Concrete Upgrade (Hydrocarbon Fire)Tunnel Hydrocarbon FireSeparating ConstructionRoof / CeilingFloor / Ceiling ConstructionHeritage Ceiling UpgradeAir Handling DuctworkAcoustic SystemSectorsBuildingInfrastructureMining Oil & GasAgricultureSub MenuFireFire Proofing Materials And SystemsFire Resisting ConstructionBuilding Code RegulationsDamper Inspection / MaintenanceFire Protection Design Fire UpgradeFire TestingFire Proof InstallationAcousticThermalProblem SolvingDivisionsManufacturingConsultancyContractingClick here for site map
Search ...
Login
Register
HomeCompanyAbout UsHistory MissionValuesAwards LAF QualityCertifications & ApprovalsHealth & SafetyEnvironmentPoliciesOrganisationLAF AustraliaLAF WorldwideLAF Hall of FameTestimonialsProductsOur ProductsOur Systems
ReferencesE-ShopContacts
Search ...
Login
Register
HomeCompanyAbout UsHistory MissionValuesAwards LAF QualityCertifications & ApprovalsHealth & SafetyEnvironmentPoliciesOrganisationLAF AustraliaLAF WorldwideLAF Hall of FameTestimonialsProductsOur ProductsOur Systems
ReferencesE-ShopContacts
Menu
Search ...
Login
Register
HomeCompanyProductsReferencesContactsARCHITECTSENGINEERSBUILDERSAPPLICATORSTechnical ThoughtsCareers
Print
PRIVACY STATEMENT
We respect everyone’s privacy and we are committed to maintaining personal information exact, private and secure. To ensure that we remain committed to this goal the LAF Group has adopted the following privacy policy.
The Privacy Policy applies globally and is based on, and complies with the Australian Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and its associated National Privacy Principles. For more information about this legislation please visit the web site of the Australian Privacy Commissioner at www.privacy.gov.au.
WHEN WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
In the course of offering and delivering services to our clients, the LAF Group collects information of a personal nature. The information collected will vary according to what we offer in return as far as services and products are concerned.
The LAF Group may collect personal information from you directly, from publicly available sources of information or from other third parties. At the time personal information is collected, LAF undertakes to take reasonable steps keep you informed on the type of purpose for the collection and your rights to access this kind of information.
When working with LAF Group we may be required to collect information about you for the purposes of meeting obligations under International Sanctions and International terrorism laws. This may include your full name, date of birth and residential address amongst other details as required under the law. Some of the personal information collected may constitute sensitive information such as your place of birth and nationality.
USE AND DISCLOSURE
We use your personal information to:
provide you with the services and products you have requested;
provide information about our range of products or services, including promotions or special offers which may be available from time to time; or comply with legal and regulatory obligations.
Unless you give your consent for your information to be used for another reason, the LAF Group will only use or disclose your personal information for the primary purpose it was collected or any reasonable secondary purpose. This may include the sending of advertising material through the post or by email. You have the right to request not to receive marketing material. If we receive such a request we will update our records accordingly and ask that you allow us a reasonable time to comply with your request.
The LAF Group is accountable for all personal information in our possession including personal information disclosed to third parties for the purposes of providing services requested by our clients. A client's consent can be express, implied, or given through an authorised representative. Consent can be withdrawn at any time, with certain exceptions. The LAF Group may, however, collect, use or disclose personal information without the client's knowledge or consent in exceptional circumstances where such collection, use or disclosure is permitted or required by law.
INFORMATION QUALITY, SECURITY, ACCESS AND CORRECTION
We take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is kept secure and protected. The LAF Group will also endeavour to keep all personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. If you believe the information we hold about you is incorrect or you would like to access your personal information you may do so by contacting us in writing (see 'contacting us' below).
CONTACTING US
Questions or feedback about this Privacy Statement, your personal information or any privacy complaints should be directed to the LAF Group Privacy Officer:
P.O. Box 13
GREENACRE NSW 2190
Tel: 02 9642 4745
Fax: 02 0742 5164
Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
If you feel that we have not adequately dealt with any privacy complaint you have made, you may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner (Australia).
Copyright © 2014 LAF Group. All Rights Reserved.
Design & Development by Archmage.
HomeTechnical ThoughtsCareersPrivacy StatementTerms & ConditionsContactsSite Map
